LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
I'm a soldier - that means I'm
Both a defendant and the judge
I am standing on both ends of the flame
Rounding curves
Overtaking life and death,
I run and fight with false shadows
No matter how many threads of
deception are woven together,
The truth shall illuminate
the face of light
Save your tears for the day
When our pain is far behind
On your feet, come with me
We are soldiers stand or die
Save your fears, take your place
Save them for the judgement day
Fast and free, follow me
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall
That concludes the report
of the SDF members who were involved in the
bomb disposal operation at Kyushu Radio Tower.
Does this decide matters?
There are still over ten kilograms
of plutonium on Dejima, after all.
Kayabuki
Prime Minister.
We will announce the deployment
of the SDF with that outline.
Any objections?
If it is the consensus of the Cabinet,
I have no objections.
The Day the
Bridge Falls
That Cabinet meeting was somewhat
forced, wasn't it?
Are we going to ignore the statement from China,
and other neighbouring Asian countries,
that we should avoid exercising military force?
Countries that have rejected the refugees
have no right to meddle in this affair,
However, our neighbouring countries concerns over
military expansion have become even more pronounced...
That reminds me...
the American Empire has contacted us.
They believe we must not set a precedent
by allowing the refugees to gain autonomy
through the use of nuclear weapons,
and that we must form a united
front in dealing with this issue,
even if it means we must
accelerate the Security Pact.
When was this?
I have heard nothing...
They don't trust you,
since they view you as pro-China.
It seems the Kayabuki Cabinet
will only last until Dejima falls.
It's about time for that asshole to notice.
Right.
We've found the vehicle abandoned at a
rest stop on the Nagasaki Expressway.
What about the plutonium?
It hasn't been found.
I see.
We have no choice.
We can't have the media getting wind of this.
We'd like you to prioritise
information manipulation
and follow our instructions
in retrieving the plutonium.
I understand that.
I will leave this to you, but...
Don't worry.
There will be no problems if
you follow my instructions.
I will now return to HQ and adjust the situation.
Understood.
The Major and the others
are on their way to Spring-8
I see.
The SDF deployment has become official.
The deployment will begin simultaneously
with the Chief Cabinet Secretary's
announcement at the seven o'clock press conference.
That's in less than an hour.
They will already be on the
move at the Dejima site.
Aramaki-San,
I don't understand the reason why
the Chief Cabinet Secretary
allowed the situation to deteriorate this far.
This will only lead to an irresolvable conflict.
Once war begins, Dejima will fall soon enough,
so it cannot become a hypothetical enemy
after the security pact is renewed.
If so, I don't think it coincides with
the Chief Cabinet Secretary's aim
to establish a military-industrial complex...
That is true,
However, if creating a
problem itself was the goal,
then it makes sense to a certain extent.
Even if the refugees surrender,
it is not as though they
will go away and disappear.
We can presume the funds that had been going to maintain the
refugee policy will consequently go to military armaments.
Well, yes,
but pressure from China will increase...
It seems there are more factors
involved than we know of.
How about this, Prime Minister?
Why don't we defer the decision to the UN,
in order to buy as much time as possible?
Major.
There's a GSDF checkpoint ahead.
I didn't think they'd let us go that easily,
What's the plan?
Major, it's me.
Prime Minister Kayabuki just
requested a UN nuclear inspection.
if all goes well, the inspection
team will arrive in two days,
If we can hand over the plutonium then,
there is a good chance that
this situation will blow over,
Can you hold out until then?
If we go into hiding somewhere, yes.
I think it'll be extremely difficult
to meet the inspection team, however.
Figure it out.
This may be the last card left to us.
I'll try.
Make sure the rookies that stayed
behind at HQ stay out of this,
in case something happens.
We'll do everything on our own from here on.
Understood.
I'll make the necessary arrangements.
Also, about the Tachikoma units...
What's wrong?
The comm link was broken.
Might be local restriction on communication
systems due to crisis legislation.
It's almost time.
I'll go to the press conference room.
Will a war break out?
The UN...?
Did Kayabuki call for them?
Yes.
Make preparations to oust her.
Understood.
Let us begin the press conference.
With the SDF's lock-down of Dejima,
Refugees Declare Independence
Using Nuclear Deterrence
large-scale traffic regulations have
been set in place in neighbouring areas.
Today, we will seize our
independence with our own hands!
LIVE
We demand
that the Japanese government recognise
Dejima as an independent nation!
LIVE
Nagasaki - Dejima
Then, we can trade freely
and live on our own!
What's wrong with that?!
We have plutonium!
The Japanese government has admitted that fact!
This is thanks to Comrade Kuze's efforts!
We'll be forever grateful to
him, and we'll never give him up!
Furthermore, the deadline
for attack is in two days.
We will set the UN nuclear inspection team's
arrival as the final chance for response;
should the refugees not respond by that time,
the preliminary attack will then begin.
That is all.
So it begins.
Now that the Chief has been cut off,
we have no choice but to make our own decisions.
Whether or not each of you goes
any further with this is up to you.
Hey!
Section 9 didn't form yesterday,
Aren't we going to pull a
running campaign against the SDF?
No.
We're going to take the plutonium to Dejima.
Dejima?
That's right.
We'll take advantage of the SDF's advance
and plunge into Dejima.
Either way, the inspection
team will come to Dejima.
Since that's the case,
we'll catch Kuze before then and hand him over,
together with the plutonium, in a neat package.
That's ridiculous, but very typical of you.
I'm coming.
I don't mind, either.
Me neither, of course.
I also have no objections, but...
Are you against it?
No.
I'll earn my keep in return for some thrills.
It's decided, then.
Major restrictions on traffic were set by
armed forces in the city of Nagasaki...
Special News Report
Nagasaki Under Martial Law
SDF Troops Deployed
Domestic Flights Temporarily Suspended
and all domestic flights were...
Nagasaki Under Martial Law
In such terms,
the decision of the government to...
How are you doing, Ishikawa?
Oh, it's you, Major.
I'm still in this miserable state.
Well, a vacation once in a
while isn't such a bad thing...
or so I'd like to say,
but I need to ask you a favour.
What is it?
I'll help with anything,
as long as I'm able to do it.
I've sent over one Tachikoma unit.
Half of the plutonium we retrieved
from the radio tower is in its pod.
Take that and go to Spring-8.
I see, so that's how it is.
I don't mind.
but what are you guys going to do?
We're going to take the
remaining plutonium to Dejima.
To Dejima?
Thought up another foolish plan, have you?
What about Togusa?
He's with the Chief at the
Prime Minister's office.
I see.
Major, I'm sorry I can't join you guys.
Be careful.
You don't know what will happen
if they begin an air raid.
Yeah.
You be careful too.
You can count on me.
I'm counting on you.
You'll see us on the news
when we hand the plutonium
over to the UN inspection team.
Don't die, Major.
Hey, Major.
Can I ask you something?
What?
When I talked to Gouda using
your external memory...
I felt bad about doing it,
but I looked into your memory about Kuze.
And?
It's not like I actually saw anything,
but it seems like you have some
special feelings towards Kuze.
What happened when you dived into his brain?
Nothing special happened.
But when I touched his memories,
it felt like he was someone I once
had a close relationship with.
A close relationship?
Yeah.
But it happened a very long time ago.
We're almost there.
Are they really going to attack?
We're prepared to make a suicide bombing strike.
Comrade Kuze said not to do anything.
Make sure we don't act first.
Then international opinion will be on our side.
We will win this fight without fighting.
Make sure you stay connected to Kuze's net.
You're Kuze Hideo, aren't you?
And you are?
I'd seen you once before overseas.
Is that so.
You were surrounded by a crowd in Taiwan, but it
seems only a few in Dejima know what you look like.
There are many who have cyberbrains here, so...
I see.
So that's why your beliefs have been
propagated among the refugees...
Of course,
I believe it to be a divine feat that could only
have been achieved with the mental fortitude
to continually respond to queries
from three million people.
However,
there was a pitfall to that.
Pitfall?
Yes.
Water flows to lower heights,
and so does the human heart.
When I returned to Dejima after
purging the thought virus,
the refugees began to connect to me right away.
I valued their thoughts
and made it my sole behavioural principle
to help them fulfil their wishes.
It wasn't too difficult to become their leader.
I put filters on the consciousness of others
and made an effort to synchronise
the consciousness of the refugees,
who are ceaselessly connected to
mine, with my ideals.
After the Great War,
I wandered through the Eurasian continent
and sought the raison d'etre
of individuals in a system.
In the process,
the refugees taught me
that humans only exist through
the intervention of others.
If you weigh your duties and your rights
and first add weight to your rights,
then you would not lose yourself
even if you were to obey social laws.
Yes.
That universal thought seemed very agreeable.
However, even the refugees
forget that and flow to lower heights
once they learn of the upper echelons via the net,
When they have power, they want to show it off,
in the same way they'd like to
try out a weapon if they had one.
Knowing that, why did you pull
the situation along this far?
Did you really believe something as far-fetched
as a revolution could be accomplished that easily?
No.
However, the revolution I have in
mind lies further on in the future.
Right now, I believe that making
people head towards the superstructure,
the revolution's goal, is a preliminary step.
Superstructure?
Is that different from hierarchy?
Yes, it is different.
The network, which is about to envelop this world,
has already turned into the infrastructure,
it has fulfilled its original purpose
and is now something different.
From there, it will achieve an existence
that will exert a counteractive
effect on the infrastructure,
from which it is inseparable,
but which is nonetheless its foundation,
and shift into a superstructure.
That is my definition of a revolution.
I don't really understand,
but is it possible to share
that belief with the refugees?
Subconsciously, we should already be sharing it,
but not yet in a concrete sense,
I gave up power in the past,
out of curiosity towards others.
If you would allow this old man a word,
you should prioritise the
reality over the ideal right now.
You can still put a stop to this.
Tachikoma.
I'm going to dive into Kuze's
cyberbrain one more time.
Give me backup.
Is that going to be okay?
Connecting won't be a problem;
whether he'll accept our message
is another story, though.
Oomura station just reported
that a chopper took off,
even though it was not scheduled for a mission.
So they've been found.
They're acting precisely like the scenario.
What is the status on EP-3C deployment?
It has already arrived above Dejima, sir.
Good.
Start there.
Jam all signals in Dejima
and turn the refugees into stand alones.
The refugees will then begin
going out of control on their own.
The net is going to get disconnected.
It seems transmissions in
Dejima are being disrupted.
Put the firewall array on standby.
Punch the message file through in one shot!
Roger!
What?
What's wrong?
They'll come here?
With the plutonium on top of that?
What are you talking about?
The net has been disconnected.
The SDF must be jamming it.
They intend to isolate the refugees.
The tanks are attacking!
It seems someone in the government
thinks the same way I do.
I will go to the barricade on Oohashi bridge.
There is a high probability
that fighting will begin.
People like you mustn't die.
If you can, please escape from Dejima.
You mustn't die, either.
There must be something you can still do.
I hope so.
How did it go?
The transmission finished a split
second before the disconnect!
Good.
Dammit, I'll get 'em!
I got him!
He was shot!
Cover us!
Gunshots!
is there combat?
Stop that!
Don't shoot! Stop!
They have nukes!
Water flows to lower heights,
and so does the human heart.
Dejima - Oohashi Bridge
What the hell?
Seems the fighting's begun.
The tanks are coming!
Destroy the bridge!
Finding out a galaxy
of planets and stars within me.
Listening to each of them
singing the same silent melody.
I've never seen such beauty
in possibility...
No smack of doubt or fear.
(Wake up)
I hear a voice.
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside
(the time is right)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
All I need,
to make all this reality.
(it's inside)
The beauty within the shell.
(deep within the shell)
(within the shell)
(Wake up)
I hear a voice
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
(the time is now)
I see inside,
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
all I need,
to make all this reality,
it's inside
right here within the shell.